const data = {
  English: [
    {
      id: "0",
      type: "multiple",
      question: "Mother Teresa received Nobel Peace Prize in the year",
      options: ["1976", "1979", "1978", "1980"],
      correctAnswer: "1979",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "1",
      type: "multiple",
      question: "Which city is Capital of India?",
      options: ["Mumbai", "Delhi", "Noida", "Chennai"],
      correctAnswer: "Delhi",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      type: "truefalse",
      question: "Tiger is the national animal of India?",
      options: [true, false],
      correctAnswer: "true",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      type: "multiple",
      question: "Which city is Capital of US?",
      options: ["LA", "Hollywood", "Washinton DC", "New York"],
      correctAnswer: "Washinton DC",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      type: "multiple",
      question: "Founder of Reliance Industries Limited is ____",
      options: [
        "Mukesh Ambani",
        "Anil Ambani",
        "Dhirubhai Ambani",
        "Akash Ambani",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "Dhirubhai Ambani",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      type: "match",
      question: "Match the following",
      sideA: ["A. Google", "B. Microsoft", "C. Meta", "D. Apple"],
      sideB: [
        "1. Tim cook",
        "2. Mark Zuckerberg",
        "3. Sundar Pichai",
        "4. Satya Nadella",
      ],
      options: [
        "A-1, B-4, C-2, D-3",
        "A-4, B-2, C-1, D-3",
        "A-3, B-4, C-2, D-1",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "A-3, B-4, C-2, D-1",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      type: "multiselect",
      question: "Which are India's current Union territories?",
      options: [
        "Andaman and Nicobar Islands",
        "Mumbai",
        "Delhi",
        "Ladakh",
        "Chennai",
        "Indore",
      ],
      correctAnswer: ["Andaman and Nicobar Islands", "Delhi", "Ladakh"],
      answer: [],
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      type: "multiselect",
      question: "Select latters which are in 'ORANGE'",
      options: ["U", "E", "O", "Z", "R"],
      correctAnswer: ["R", "E", "O"],
      answer: [],
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      type: "match",
      question: "Match the following",
      sideA: ["A. Canada", "B. India", "C. US", "D. UAE"],
      sideB: ["1. New York", "2. Dubai", "3. Toronto", "4. Mumbai"],
      options: [
        "A-1, B-4, C-2, D-3",
        "A-4, B-2, C-1, D-3",
        "A-3, B-4, C-1, D-2",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "A-3, B-4, C-1, D-2",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
  ],
  Hindi: [
    {
      id: "9",
      type: "multiple",
      question:
        "भारत के अंदर प्रथम स्थापित परमाणु-संयंत्र (Atomic Plant) इनमें से कौन सा है ?",
      options: [
        "तारापुर परमाणु संयंत्र",
        "कैटेनोम परमाणु संयंत्र",
        "कुडनकुलम परमाणु संयंत्र",
        "अन्य",
      ],
      correctAnswer: "तारापुर परमाणु संयंत्र",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      type: "multiple",
      question: "कितने सालों के बाद राष्ट्रीय जनगणना की जाती है ?",
      options: ["8", "15", "5", "10"],
      correctAnswer: "10",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "11",
      type: "multiple",
      question:
        "इनमें से सुपर मून के समय चाँद लगभग कितना प्रतिशत बड़ा दिखता है?",
      options: ["5", "14", "50", "22"],
      correctAnswer: "14",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
    {
      id: "12",
      type: "multiple",
      question: "____ में अधिकतर संख्या में भाषाएं बोली जाती हैं",
      options: ["ब्रिटेन", "यू. एस. ए", "भारत", "फ्रांस"],
      correctAnswer: "भारत",
      answer: "",
      isAnswered: false,
    },
  ],
};

export default data;
